<!--
  This is copied from SizeUp.Web/Areas/Widget/Views/Advertising/Index.cshtml ,
  but slightly enhanced to work with more flexible queries.
  TODO(twilson) after Sizeup 1/2 decision: re-centralize this sort of markup
  so that website and reporting code use the same report text.
-->
<reportText>
  <advertising>
    <userAdvice>
      <p>
          This is a list of postal codes with the highest <kpi value="revenuePerCapita">amount of revenue generated per resident</kpi> in the <industry/> industry.
          If the industry serves the local area, then residents or businesses within the area are spending more than average.
          Central business districts will have inflated revenue per capita figures because they serve as destinations for 
          commerce and they have few residents.
      </p>
      <p>
          This is a list of ZIP codes with the <kpi value="underservedMarkets">lowest amount of revenue generated per resident</kpi> in the <industry/> industry.
          If the industry serves the local area, then residents or businesses within the area are spending less than average,
          which may mean that that there is opportunity for new businesses within that industry to take advantage of untapped markets.
      </p>
      <p>
          This is a list of ZIP codes with the highest <kpi value="averageRevenue">average business revenue</kpi> in the <industry/> industry.
          You should consider using this list if you are selling to businesses and want to target areas where
           the average business is very successful.
      </p>
      <p>
          This is a list of ZIP codes with the highest <kpi value="totalRevenue">combined business revenue</kpi> in the <industry/> industry.
          You should consider using this list if you are selling to businesses or consumers and want to know where the most
          money is being made in your industry.
      </p>
      <p>
          This is a list of ZIP codes with the highest <kpi value="householdIncome">median household incomes</kpi>. Use this list if your products or 
          services are targeted at consumers with specific income levels.
      </p>
      <p>
          This is a list of ZIP codes showing <kpi value="totalEmployees">Total Employees</kpi> for the <industry/> industry.
      </p>
    </userAdvice>
  </advertising>
</reportText>
